Ever heard of coil?
It's not just another online class.
It's a revolutionary way to connect students across the globe.
Imagine working side by side with students from different countries,
tackling shared projects and building trust, all while guided by
expert educators.
COIL stands for Collaborative Online International Learning, Blending virtual interactions
with face to face sessions for a truly multicultural learning
experience.
It's not a lifeless MOOC or just a social media
group.
It's structured, engaging, and deeply collaborative.
Students and faculty work together to define goals, solve problems,
and share their insights.
From icebreakers to final presentations, col builds connections that last.
So are you ready to step into a global classroom?
Check out the padlet, introduce yourself and join us on
this incredible journey.
It's not just education, it's transformation.